The iCumulate Token Sale Smart Contract Address
Smart Contract Contribution Address.

Our smart contract contribution address is:
0x9cb22d847750eaa06de1fb64cc87ce10a9d41b48

We will not post our smart contract contribution address on our website. 
Instead, we have announced it on our Twitter, Telegram, Youtube, Medium and Github channels. 

Verification and Cross-checking:
There is ONLY ONE smart contract address for our Token Sale. We highly recommend you to verify this address against at least 2–3 of our official channels before triggering your ETH transactions. 

Angelos, our CEO, features in the following video to show the smart contract address, for all of you to cross-check the authenticity of the contribution address.


Verification one - Youtube Video featuring Angelos:
https://youtu.be/zdVY-sJAatU

Verification two- Clearify smart contract authenticity process:
https://www.clearify.io/
 
Verification three - Telegram Channel Announcement:
https://www.t.me/iCumulateChat
 
Verification four- Medium Publication:
https://medium.com/@icumulate/the-icu...
 
Verification five- Github:
https://github.com/iCumulate

Verification six - Twitter post:
https://twitter.com/iCumulate_io
 
We will NOT communicate the contract address through email or Telegram private message.